("Can't Take My Eyes Off You")
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off you ♪
♪ You'd be like heaven to touch ♪
♪ I wanna hold you so much ♪
♪ At long last love has arrived ♪
♪ And I thank God I'm alive ♪
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off you ♪
♪ Pardon the way that I stare ♪
♪ There's nothing else to compare ♪
♪ The sight of you leaves me weak ♪
♪ There are no words left to speak ♪
♪ But if you feel like I feel ♪
♪ Please let me know that it's real ♪
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off you ♪
♪ I love you baby ♪
♪ And if it's quite all right ♪
♪ I need you baby ♪
♪ To warm the lonely nights ♪
♪ I love you baby ♪
♪ Trust in me when I say ♪
♪ Oh pretty baby ♪
♪ Don't bring me down I pray ♪
♪ Now that I've found you stay ♪
♪ And let me love you, baby ♪
♪ Let me love you ♪
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off you ♪
♪ You'd be like heaven to touch ♪
♪ I wanna hold you so much ♪
♪ At long last love has arrived ♪
♪ And I thank God I'm alive ♪
♪ You're just too good to be true ♪
♪ Can't take my eyes off You ♪
♪ I love you baby ♪
♪ And if it's quite all right ♪
♪ I need you baby ♪
♪ To warm the lonely nights ♪
♪ I love you baby ♪
♪ Trust in me when I say ♪
♪ Oh pretty baby ♪
♪ Don't bring me down I pray ♪
♪ Now that I've found you stay ♪
♪ Oh pretty baby ♪
♪ Trust in me when I say ♪